{
    "id": "d14efe5fcc7944fea4cd7b0a3a15d998",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Of the two sisters, Susie is the ……………………..",
            "description": "We do not normally use the superlative to talk about two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mumbai is …………………………. from Kochi than Bangalore.",
            "description": "Farther shows distance.",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I want ……………………….. information.",
            "description": "Further means additional.",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Namita is my …………………….. sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This painting is superior ……………………….. that.",
            "description": "The adjectives superior, inferior, junior and senior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured were taken to the ………………………. hospital.",
            "description": "Nearest indicates distance. Next indicates order.",
            "answers": [
                "nearest",
                "next"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "As soon as she finished one project, she started working on the ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nearest",
                "next"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must act without any ……………………….. delay.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the ………………………. man in the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this the ……………………….. edition of this book?",
            "description": "Latest means the most recent.",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the ………………………. of the two.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "cleverest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting was attended by ………………………. parents.",
            "description": "A few means some.",
            "answers": [
                "the few",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}